Guide to the Stanford University, Sponsored Projects Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1993-130
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 9/1/86 - 3/15/87 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 3/16/87 - 8/15/87 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 8/16/87 - 1/31/88 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 2/1/88 - 6/15/88 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 6/16/88 - 11/31/88 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 12/88 (Box 1, Folder 12)